PROFILE

Experienced Senior Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in SBA.

Skilled in Sql Server Database, Databases, ASP.NET, MVC, Web Applications, and ShearPoint (Full Stack).

Strong engineering professional with a bachelor's degree focused in Computer Science from Princess Noura Bin Abdulrahman.

CONTACT:

PHONE:

(966) 508 032070

EMAIL

Afnan.alhamidi@gmail.com

SKILS:

Python	50%
c# , c ++	90%
PHP Laravel	50%
Bootstrap	85%
Sql Server	90%
jQuery , JavaScript , Ajax	85%
HTML5, CSS3	95%
SharePoint	90%
ASP.NET (MVC 5)	80%

AFNAN ALHAMIDI

Full Stack Web Developer (.Net)

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree

2013 - 2014

University of Princess Nora Bin Abdulrahman - Riyadh - Saudi Arabia

Specialization: Computer Science **Average:** 4.04

Secondary degree

2008 - 2009

High School from Al-Jeel School - Riyadh - Saudi Arabia

Specialization: Science Average: 100%

WORK EXPERIENCE

SBA - Full Stack Web Developer (.Net) and shearPoint

2017 - Present

Designer and developer for Websites by ASP.NET & C# AND SQL Server and shearPoint

SBA - Web Developer (.Net)

2015 - 2017

Designer and developer for Websites by ASP.NET & C# AND SQL Server and ASP.NET (MVC5)

Horizon Information - Web Developer (ASP.Net)

2013-2014

Web Developer for Web sites using (ASP.Net & c#)

TRAINING

University Of Princess Noura Bin Abdulrahman

GOT: ICDL Certification

Saudi Broadcasting Authority (SBA)

GOT: Intern Certificate for the Cycle to Collect Information Using Social Networking

AdAA and King Salman Youth Center

GOT: Certificate of the training program for (Kpi's) (3 Days)

King Saud University

GOT: Certificate of the training program for (PMI) (36 hours)

COURSES

- Certificate of Attendance at a Course on Microsoft Software Products (One Day).
- Certificate of Attendance International Conference and Exhibition for Training and Development at the University Of Princess Noura Bin Abdulrahman (3 Days).
- Creativity and best practices in the management, governance and security of information technology in Riyadh chamber (3 Days).